carlsbadcravings.com 2019-05-06

# Copyright and Privacy Policy - Carlsbad Cravings

##  **COPYRIGHT**

All content, including recipes, photographs, and posts published on CarlsbadCravings.com is property of Carlsbad Cravings (Jennifer Sattley).  If you would like to share a recipe and/or photo on your website, please only include one photo.  You may include a description without the ingredient lists and/or instructions.  Please LINK BACK to the original recipe, giving Carlsbad Cravings full credit.

Publishing full recipes from Carlsbad Cravings and/or ingredients and instructions is strictly prohibited.

##  **PRIVACY POLICY**

Carlsbad Cravings strongly believes in keeping your personal information confidential.  Carlsbad Cravings safeguards your personal information and never sells it to third parties. The following policy describes what information we collect and how it is used and shared.

##  **What Information do we collect and why?**

###  **LOG FILES**

As with most other websites, we use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used.  A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive.  The data collected helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs.  We  _only_  use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system after 26 months.

 _No personal information is stored in these log files._  The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, which is the company on your internet bill), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Safari or Chrome, etc), the time you visited our site, and which pages you visited throughout our site.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in  _no_  way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

###  **ADVERTISING**

We may use advertising service vendors to help present advertisements on the website, including Mediavine.  These vendors may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies.  These technologies help analyze web traffic and allows web applications to respond to you as an individual.  The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.   It also determines whether you have seen a particular advertisement before and to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements.

In using cookies, these vendors may collect non-personal data such as your browser type, your operating system, Web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other clickstream data.  The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by these advertising service vendors is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours, and Carlsbad Cravings disclaims all liability in connection therewith.  We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers.  If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

###  **COMMENTS**

Carlsbad Cravings collects as little information as possible from users looking to post comments.  We will typically collect a name (either real or alias), personal website (optional), and e-mail address.  None of your information will be shared with third parties.   Your name and website may be displayed on the site if you post a comment or a message in the forum.  However, your e-mail address and privacy will always be kept secure.

##  **SECURE DATA**

Carlsbad Cravings is committed to ensuring that your information is secure and never sells it to third parties. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.  Should there be a data breach, we will advise users within 72 hours of that breach.

 ** _Use of this website indicates that you accept this policy._**
